<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2019-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Civilization as an Illusion</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190106civilization-as-an-illusion.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190106civilization-as-an-illusion.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-07T01:33:21+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Because this is the end of civilization! People like you don't want to work or learn anything because they're too busy with their remote control television or playing with their hula-hoops! And before you know it, that's where we're at!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as I can tell what's hold on this civilization is lying. To lie, we need some sort of communication. A channel where information flows. But information is not enough. Some sort of consciousness is neccesary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, I'm with Jaynes. To be conscious it takes what you least expect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is once we learned to talk to each other that the gods were away. It is when we created the laws that a civilization was born. To hold millions, a mechanism like laws or a constitution was enough. It is enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But all that it's an illusion, I believe. It only takes a few thoughts to release that this civilization is hang on a thread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, when will we start over?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190105artificial-intelligence.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190105artificial-intelligence.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-05T17:19:50+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some people worry that artificial intelligence will make us feel inferior, but then, anybody in his right mind should have an inferiority complex every time he looks at a flower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my pursue to conquer the galaxy one thing I certainly need. That is the use of artificial intelligence. My goal is to conquer myrmecology as much as possible to have an workforce that allow me, at some point, to harvest raw materials in space. However, I don't need to create dangerous artificial intelligence as some well-known celebrities are worried about to be created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm worried but for entirely different reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, I don't think the A.I. we'll create will be &lt;em&gt;evil&lt;/em&gt; by itself. It might be &lt;em&gt;evil&lt;/em&gt; because the humans who coded.
Second, I don't think we will reach intelligence like ours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't think we will reach it because of the same reason I'm not looking to create it. That is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Existence is pain.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I see consciousness as an illusion.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It will be like having babes we then make slaves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time we are capable of creating General Artificial Intelligence, we will seattle for less: an enhancement of our own intelligence hopefully for good.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Existential Debt</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190104existential-debt.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190104existential-debt.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-05T00:22:11+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Take it moment by moment, and you will find that we are all, as I've said before, bugs in amber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have this proposal: &lt;em&gt;Existential Debt&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it can be better explained by example. So here it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine we are embarking in creating a startup. The idea is to capitalize on wood furniture. We have the trees, the tools, the workforce, we have it all. We do it all. From raw materials to the end product, we work. Everything goes fine for years and years. The question is: what is the existential debt of that startup?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of the Existential Debt is that no matter what it's done, you always get some.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is based on two concepts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everything is interconnected and the benefit of something is merely in the context in which is examined. What seems to be &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; for someone, it's &lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt; for someone else or something else.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everything decays or everything is changing whichever way you want to see it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The startup to avoid screwing the forest, i.e., plants more trees. In doing so, it changes the environment around and that may cause the lives of other beings directly o indirectly. That in turn affects everything around. It goes &lt;em&gt;well&lt;/em&gt; since the startup goes on and the reforestation happens but something get messed up in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The startup to avoid chemical wasted, invests in research and finds a way to stop screwing the environment. In doing so, something is affected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, there is no free lunch. Something changes for &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Briefly:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a Cosmos where there is no meaning, only the one that sentient beings choose to have, the Existential Debt is an idea that helps to be aware of our actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This came to me while I was reading a book on systems thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Games as ATM</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20181226game-as-atm.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20181226game-as-atm.html</id>
    <published>2018-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-02T01:28:17+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In the end, we self-perceiving, self-inventing, locked-in mirages are little miracles of self-reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My bet is consciousness is an illusion. A very well perpetuate illusion. Just like the reality our brains created of whatever is really &lt;em&gt;outside&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ATM. Alien Time Machine. Although, what I wanted to write was AMT: Analogy-making Tool. Games, all kinds, I see them as analogy-making tools. That is important since I part of the people who believes that's the key for artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I have to confess, I don't want to create artificial intelligence since I believe existence is pain. Why would I want to &lt;em&gt;bring&lt;/em&gt; something or someone to this cosmos?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started a personal game last year without seeing how important it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game consist in playing with words to create different meanings. You &lt;em&gt;*c&lt;/em&gt;an play, r8?. The more u play it, the more you realize how crazy the mind is. You can find meaning in everything or rather say you can make meaning after any thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what people who enjoy metal know each other? Because they &lt;em&gt;met&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;al&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know designers are the thing? Because they are &lt;em&gt;de&lt;/em&gt;sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can make more complicated mixtures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why a &lt;em&gt;re&lt;/em&gt;quest is not repeatable and instead a pet addiction?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt;on you get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Perspective and Representation are the Sides of the Same Coin</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20181223perspective-representation-sides-of-the-same-coin.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20181223perspective-representation-sides-of-the-same-coin.html</id>
    <published>2018-12-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-23T15:58:59+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The rationalization that took place during the so-called "scientific revolution" is not of the mind, of the eye, of philosophy, but of the &lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;.Why is perspective such an inportant invention?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, perspective is representation, internally (brain) and/or externally (reality). You probably have noticed that because you have encountered problems in your life. You tried to solve them with no results. Then, for some reason, you tried another approach. You saw the situations in a different way. You noticed new stuff. And soon you saw the solution. It was right there. How I'd haven't seen it!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it was being cooked in the back of your head. Maybe it was a different version your brain twist it again and again until it &lt;em&gt;fit&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I dunno.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact is that you found them and the only thing that &lt;em&gt;changed&lt;/em&gt; was you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There is no spoon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Mind at Play</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20181222a-mind-at-play.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20181222a-mind-at-play.html</id>
    <published>2018-12-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-23T03:50:55+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of the beliefs I currently hold is that the more you read, the more you're starting to see things more hmm holistically. You see connections here and there from completely unrelated fields. My bet is that the brain or the structure that holds knowledge does not &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; which is what. It take the input, connect them, and give an output regardless of what the input was.
What I find interesting is how I came to believe that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It came by merging a few unrelated fields!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first realization was that people who were blind since birth dream with noises. No image. It makes sense since the brain doesn't have any visual input to distort or play with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second realization was what happen when you get into the dark tank and &lt;em&gt;inhibit&lt;/em&gt; senses, external stimuli. You start hallucinating. I don't know if that is because of the lack of stimuli but I thought of what a blind person could hallucinate. I thought of sound like what they dream, nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the third realization was that the brain creates the reality based on the senses or input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't remember the order in which I learned those things but once I got the last one, the belief poped up into my head. It just made sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mind was playing with things but it was not aware or know the rules to what to mix with or not mix with. To what to relate or not to relate. To what make sense to play or not. It just does it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What could possible find if I read more unrelated fields, I wonder.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
