<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2019-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Plan</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190115plan.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190115plan.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-15T00:40:28+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The future is already here - it's just not evenly distributed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Planning is one of those things that humans are into it. I don't know if the reason is fear of failing, death, disappointment, etc. Maybe it's because the brain is a pattern recognition machine and a plan has structure, has a pattern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the etymologies of plan is &lt;em&gt;level or flat surface&lt;/em&gt;. It reminds of phrases like &lt;em&gt;don't go under water&lt;/em&gt;. Under water? It's like water is a 2D thing. Water for the brain is a surface. Plan is a flat surface. I don't know why my brain makes these silly connections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I think planning might not be the answer. I don't think the Cosmos plans for this reality and yet look it run!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>No Leaders</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190114no-leaders.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190114no-leaders.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-15T00:02:55+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Make it so&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things like &lt;a href="https://1scyem2bunjw1ghzsf1cjwwn-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/thinking-forth-color.pdf"&gt;Forth Thinking&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LOOP_(programming_language)"&gt;LOOP Programming&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://science.sciencemag.org/content/327/5964/439"&gt;Rules for Biologically Inspired Adaptive Network Design&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://books.google.com.mx/books?id=3DocCGB0cRkC&amp;amp;pg=PT348&amp;amp;lpg=PT348&amp;amp;dq=hanoi+towers+steven+pinker&amp;amp;source=bl&amp;amp;ots=rYQQ7O7Nt_&amp;amp;sig=kUt4XqOZYs-5I4eHogbvXF2AODs&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwijpqiLve7fAhVQ2qwKHUw7BQkQ6AEwB3oECAgQAQ#v=onepage&amp;amp;q=hanoi%20towers%20steven%20pinker&amp;amp;f=false"&gt;the Tower of Hanoi Analogy&lt;/a&gt; make me think that perhaps we are doing everything wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, we should think like mathematicians, we should be slow thinkers. Remove everything that rush us into get things done as fast as we can. Take our time. Yeah, life's too short but it will get shorter for everybody on this planet if we don't stop fast thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brain is a powerful machine but it's not perfect. We need to take our time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make it so.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Binary System</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190113binary-system.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190113binary-system.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-13T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-14T23:53:06+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A reliable way to make people believe in falsehoods is frequent repetition, because familiarity is not easily distinguished from truth. Authoritarian institutions and marketers have always known this fact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it possible the human civilization we our so proud of is merely the product of our fast thinking and, therefore, it has a terrible foundation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The complexity of this civilization baffles to the point that I'm not sure how much time before we annihilate ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Dauthuz</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190112dauthuz.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190112dauthuz.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-11T15:00:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Man is literally split in two: he has an awareness of his own splendid uniqueness in that he sticks out of nature with a towering majesty, and yet he goes back into the ground a few feet in order to blindly and dumbly rot and disappear forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The condition we all are perhaps is the reason of our self-destructive behavoir. It's like we don't want to be happy, whatever that is.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Science</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190111science.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190111science.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-10T16:41:13+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We fight inequality in knowledge access across the world. The scientific knowledge should be available for every person regardless of their income, social status, geographical location and etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember that I was discourage to going into Astronomy. In his defense, my father was just protecting me. He wanted a future where I can survive after his gone. I think that shows the roots of the problem with this civilization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember I got into PhD program because I was in love with science, however, I got discourage by watching how things where done in the institution I was researching. In their defense, their were looking after themselves (money and ego). So I dropped out after 4 years of working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I'm working on a project that will take me at least 50 years. Projects of such magnitude clearly cannot be done by one person, me. I'm well aware that I need to find other people. I depend on them. While trying to find such people, I stumbled upon the same hidden issues I mentioned before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we have to pay for scientific papers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we want to have a civilization?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we say we are superior species when we clearly live by the rules of Nature?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our civilization is based on so many illusions what we are not willing to challenge. Is it our nature to be followers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is that that a country with 60% of poverty is ruled by the minority? By numbers, they should take the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why we are still bicameral men?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Misanthropic</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190110misanthropic.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190110misanthropic.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-09T16:31:30+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Humans are a deeply flawed and a destructive species that is responsible for the suffering and deaths of billions of other humans and non-human animals. If that level of destruction were caused by another species we would rapidly recommend that new members of that species not be brought into existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I'd like to share a revelation that I've had during my time here. It came to me when I tried to classify your species and I realized that you're not actually mammals. Every mammal on this planet instinctively develops a natural equilibrium with the surrounding environment but you humans do not. You move to an area and you multiply and multiply until every natural resource is consumed and the only way you can survive is to spread to another area. There is another organism on this planet that follows the same pattern. Do you know what it is? A virus. Human beings are a disease, a cancer of this planet. You're a plague and we are the cure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
