<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2018-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Games as ATM</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20181226game-as-atm.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20181226game-as-atm.html</id>
    <published>2018-12-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-02T01:28:17+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In the end, we self-perceiving, self-inventing, locked-in mirages are little miracles of self-reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My bet is consciousness is an illusion. A very well perpetuate illusion. Just like the reality our brains created of whatever is really &lt;em&gt;outside&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ATM. Alien Time Machine. Although, what I wanted to write was AMT: Analogy-making Tool. Games, all kinds, I see them as analogy-making tools. That is important since I part of the people who believes that's the key for artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I have to confess, I don't want to create artificial intelligence since I believe existence is pain. Why would I want to &lt;em&gt;bring&lt;/em&gt; something or someone to this cosmos?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started a personal game last year without seeing how important it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game consist in playing with words to create different meanings. You &lt;em&gt;*c&lt;/em&gt;an play, r8?. The more u play it, the more you realize how crazy the mind is. You can find meaning in everything or rather say you can make meaning after any thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what people who enjoy metal know each other? Because they &lt;em&gt;met&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;al&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know designers are the thing? Because they are &lt;em&gt;de&lt;/em&gt;sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can make more complicated mixtures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why a &lt;em&gt;re&lt;/em&gt;quest is not repeatable and instead a pet addiction?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt;on you get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Perspective and Representation are the Sides of the Same Coin</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20181223perspective-representation-sides-of-the-same-coin.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20181223perspective-representation-sides-of-the-same-coin.html</id>
    <published>2018-12-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-23T15:58:59+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The rationalization that took place during the so-called "scientific revolution" is not of the mind, of the eye, of philosophy, but of the &lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;.Why is perspective such an inportant invention?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, perspective is representation, internally (brain) and/or externally (reality). You probably have noticed that because you have encountered problems in your life. You tried to solve them with no results. Then, for some reason, you tried another approach. You saw the situations in a different way. You noticed new stuff. And soon you saw the solution. It was right there. How I'd haven't seen it!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it was being cooked in the back of your head. Maybe it was a different version your brain twist it again and again until it &lt;em&gt;fit&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I dunno.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact is that you found them and the only thing that &lt;em&gt;changed&lt;/em&gt; was you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There is no spoon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Mind at Play</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20181222a-mind-at-play.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20181222a-mind-at-play.html</id>
    <published>2018-12-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-23T03:50:55+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of the beliefs I currently hold is that the more you read, the more you're starting to see things more hmm holistically. You see connections here and there from completely unrelated fields. My bet is that the brain or the structure that holds knowledge does not &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; which is what. It take the input, connect them, and give an output regardless of what the input was.
What I find interesting is how I came to believe that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It came by merging a few unrelated fields!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first realization was that people who were blind since birth dream with noises. No image. It makes sense since the brain doesn't have any visual input to distort or play with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second realization was what happen when you get into the dark tank and &lt;em&gt;inhibit&lt;/em&gt; senses, external stimuli. You start hallucinating. I don't know if that is because of the lack of stimuli but I thought of what a blind person could hallucinate. I thought of sound like what they dream, nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the third realization was that the brain creates the reality based on the senses or input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't remember the order in which I learned those things but once I got the last one, the belief poped up into my head. It just made sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mind was playing with things but it was not aware or know the rules to what to mix with or not mix with. To what to relate or not to relate. To what make sense to play or not. It just does it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What could possible find if I read more unrelated fields, I wonder.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
