<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2019-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Science</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190111science.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190111science.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-10T16:41:13+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We fight inequality in knowledge access across the world. The scientific knowledge should be available for every person regardless of their income, social status, geographical location and etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember that I was discourage to going into Astronomy. In his defense, my father was just protecting me. He wanted a future where I can survive after his gone. I think that shows the roots of the problem with this civilization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember I got into PhD program because I was in love with science, however, I got discourage by watching how things where done in the institution I was researching. In their defense, their were looking after themselves (money and ego). So I dropped out after 4 years of working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I'm working on a project that will take me at least 50 years. Projects of such magnitude clearly cannot be done by one person, me. I'm well aware that I need to find other people. I depend on them. While trying to find such people, I stumbled upon the same hidden issues I mentioned before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we have to pay for scientific papers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we want to have a civilization?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do we say we are superior species when we clearly live by the rules of Nature?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our civilization is based on so many illusions what we are not willing to challenge. Is it our nature to be followers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is that that a country with 60% of poverty is ruled by the minority? By numbers, they should take the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why we are still bicameral men?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Misanthropic</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190110misanthropic.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190110misanthropic.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-09T16:31:30+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Humans are a deeply flawed and a destructive species that is responsible for the suffering and deaths of billions of other humans and non-human animals. If that level of destruction were caused by another species we would rapidly recommend that new members of that species not be brought into existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I'd like to share a revelation that I've had during my time here. It came to me when I tried to classify your species and I realized that you're not actually mammals. Every mammal on this planet instinctively develops a natural equilibrium with the surrounding environment but you humans do not. You move to an area and you multiply and multiply until every natural resource is consumed and the only way you can survive is to spread to another area. There is another organism on this planet that follows the same pattern. Do you know what it is? A virus. Human beings are a disease, a cancer of this planet. You're a plague and we are the cure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Es War Einmal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190109es-war-einmal.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190109es-war-einmal.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-09T16:18:15+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Nous ne vivons pas dans un pays, Nous vivons dans une langue&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wenn nur die Geschichten am Ende beginnen wurden, ware eine andere Sache die Natur eines sinnlosen Universums&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sha'ir</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190108shair.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190108shair.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-08T19:11:10+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This little box of mine? It's my collection. Contains lots of stuff but mostly questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; something is to what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Til this day I have no idea what knowning actually is. I'm full of doubts and questions. Answers don't seem to be my thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sha'ir&lt;/em&gt;, the knower.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Shag</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190107shag.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190107shag.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-08T19:03:28+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Human memory demands light before heavy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shag&lt;/em&gt; a word in Akkadian that seems to mean &lt;strong&gt;in&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;inside&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that why shagging is used to mean having sex?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or is it just part of the Dopeler effect? Where stupid ideas tend to seem smarter when they come at you rapdly?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beats me.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Civilization as an Illusion</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/20190106civilization-as-an-illusion.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/20190106civilization-as-an-illusion.html</id>
    <published>2019-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-07T01:33:21+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Because this is the end of civilization! People like you don't want to work or learn anything because they're too busy with their remote control television or playing with their hula-hoops! And before you know it, that's where we're at!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as I can tell what's hold on this civilization is lying. To lie, we need some sort of communication. A channel where information flows. But information is not enough. Some sort of consciousness is neccesary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, I'm with Jaynes. To be conscious it takes what you least expect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is once we learned to talk to each other that the gods were away. It is when we created the laws that a civilization was born. To hold millions, a mechanism like laws or a constitution was enough. It is enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But all that it's an illusion, I believe. It only takes a few thoughts to release that this civilization is hang on a thread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, when will we start over?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
